<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on tellMeY</title>
    <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on tellMeY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 03:06:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tellmeY18.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Choose Your Cells</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/choose-your-cells/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 03:06:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/choose-your-cells/</guid>
      <description>I have always supported the digitization of various routine processes on campus, including the allocation of hostel rooms. Throughout my time at NITC, I believed that technology could play a crucial role in bridging the gap between the administration and students. However, the recent implementation of the Hostel app is a prime example of how such tools can be poorly executed.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t the first time we have seen software tools being developed for our own use on campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/pages/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/pages/projects/</guid>
      <description>This page will showcase all my projects.
Index Of NITC : A website to consolidate everything related to NITC into a single website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I moved on from my Xs and reasons why you should do the same</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 01:16:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/issues/</guid>
      <description>So you fell into another clickbait. You might have clicked the link hoping for me ranting about my love life. You aren&amp;rsquo;t completely wrong. This is actually a rant about my love life, just not the one that you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with. I&amp;rsquo;ll start this off by letting you know that I&amp;rsquo;ve found happiness with Hyprland and to date I can&amp;rsquo;t think of anyone else to mimic the experience.
My life with the X display server started during my school days when we were introduced to the It@school OS custom made by the Kerala Government for the State board highschool education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m an engineering student based in Calicut. My focus area for the past few years has been GNU /Linux computing and decentralized social networks. I&amp;rsquo;m also well-versed in event management and teaching. I have a strong desire to continue honing my skills and pursuing my interests in technology and education. Create a basic website Showcase this to gain infinite social credits Conquer the World 💀 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hugo</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/learning-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:51:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/learning-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Vacation season is here, and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen my peers posting their memories as blog posts on various platforms. Journaling was on the list of things to do for me this year, and as with almost everything else, I struggled with consistency and had to let go of journaling in Mastodon halfway. Blogs are usually fun to read, and the good ones will never bore you with depressing content. The primary AIM of setting up this blog post is to familiarize myself with the set of tools a developer should have.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
