<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on tellMeY</title>
    <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on tellMeY</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:53:40 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FridayNightFoss</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/fridaynightfoss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:53:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/fridaynightfoss/</guid>
      <description>What better way to celebrate the Hacker culture than to build something that you love overnight. Me and afraz visited the TinkerSpace back when we went to attend the Debutsav, AIM and I spent sometime later on the hackerspace when he came to attend the Kochi foss monthly meetup. We both registered our names there and I got to know about their Saturday Hacknight. I really liked their Idea and wanted to implement the same for NITC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CloudedBySmoke</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/cloudedbysmoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:28:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/cloudedbysmoke/</guid>
      <description>Rrephrased by ChatGPT to reduce redundancy. The fact that today marks the beginning of the academic year has no influence on my decision to write this now. Unlike my past attempts to establish habits for consistency, I am well aware that I won&amp;rsquo;t be writing again anytime soon. I&amp;rsquo;ve struggled with maintaining consistency in anything productive, often feeling that I have a short attention span and find it challenging to sustain efforts for tasks that require consistency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choose Your Cells</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/choose-your-cells/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 03:06:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/choose-your-cells/</guid>
      <description>I have always supported the digitization of various routine processes on campus, including the allocation of hostel rooms. Throughout my time at NITC, I believed that technology could play a crucial role in bridging the gap between the administration and students. However, the recent implementation of the Hostel app is a prime example of how such tools can be poorly executed.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t the first time we have seen software tools being developed for our own use on campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I moved on from my Xs and reasons why you should do the same</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 01:16:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/issues/</guid>
      <description>So you fell into another clickbait. You might have clicked the link hoping for me ranting about my love life. You aren&amp;rsquo;t completely wrong. This is actually a rant about my love life, just not the one that you&amp;rsquo;re familiar with. I&amp;rsquo;ll start this off by letting you know that I&amp;rsquo;ve found happiness with Hyprland and to date I can&amp;rsquo;t think of anyone else to mimic the experience.
My life with the X display server started during my school days when we were introduced to the It@school OS custom made by the Kerala Government for the State board highschool education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Hugo</title>
      <link>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/learning-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:51:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tellmeY18.github.io/posts/learning-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Vacation season is here, and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen my peers posting their memories as blog posts on various platforms. Journaling was on the list of things to do for me this year, and as with almost everything else, I struggled with consistency and had to let go of journaling in Mastodon halfway. Blogs are usually fun to read, and the good ones will never bore you with depressing content. The primary AIM of setting up this blog post is to familiarize myself with the set of tools a developer should have.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
